[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Octo is a prefix meaning eight.  An Octopus has eight legs. An octagon has exactly 8 sides.  An Octogenarian is at least 8 decades old.  What is the eighth month?", "correct_answer": "August", "incorrect_answers": ["November", "October", "September"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the beginning of the movie Jaws, a girl goes out for a swim and is eaten by the great white shark. What is the girls name?", "correct_answer": "Chrissy", "incorrect_answers": ["Penelope", "Sarah", "Eli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This city is Kenyas capital and the most populous city in East Africa.", "correct_answer": "Nairobi", "incorrect_answers": ["Cape Town", "Port Louis", "Tripoli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie House of 1000 Corpses George Wydell interrogated Captain Spaulding.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Origami is a hobby and an art of Chinese origin that uses solely what material for its creations?", "correct_answer": "Paper", "incorrect_answers": ["Stone", "Wood", "Flowers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scarlett Johansson released her first music album in 2008.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Japanese dried seaweed sheets used in the preparation of sushi?", "correct_answer": "Nori", "incorrect_answers": ["Onigiri", "Sashimi", "Yakisoba"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The oldest surviving violin, date-stamped on the inside, is the Charles IX, made in 1564 by which luthier?", "correct_answer": "Andrea Amati", "incorrect_answers": ["Antonio Stradivari", "Pietro Guarneri", "Andrea Guarneri"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor played young Johnny Blaze in the 2007 film Ghost Rider?", "correct_answer": "Matt Long", "incorrect_answers": ["Laurence Bruels", "Donal Logue", "Wes Bently"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country had the highest production of carrots in 2005?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Egypt", "Russia", "USA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are their any complete dodo specimens anywhere in the world?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the movie The Wild Bunch released?", "correct_answer": "1969", "incorrect_answers": ["1967", "1971", "1968"]}]